Just to be clear, I'm blocking anybody defending Democrats.
Anybody who comes in here defending Democrats, you're getting blocked.
That's where we're at now.
Even the attempt to suggest that Democrats are not duplicitous or that they're operating
in some form or fashion on the electoral level in accordance with Jeffrey Epstein
on an above-the-board measure is beyond my scope of comprehension.
I can't keep willful ignorance in my space.
So when you come in my comments and you say things like,
you know, suggesting Stacey Plaskett is bought is a dangerous slope,
I can't, I won't allow that.
Because we're so far down the slope that anyone talking like that is a distraction
to those of us trying to climb the mountain because we've seen the mountaintop.
So glad to keyword I want to see.
We'll be sure to vote.
So thank you.
That's what I hope I praise you.